Toggle navigation [](https://workupload.com/)

Privacy Policy
==============

The purpose of this data protection declaration is to inform you, as a user, about the collection of personal data on this website. We therefore consider it important to present all essential information for the protection of your data as transparently as possible. However, if there are any questions, questions or need for clarification, please do not hesitate to contact us.  

A. The data controller

in the sense of the General Data Protection Regulation (Art. 4 para. 7 GDPR) and the other national data protection laws and data protection provisions is:  
  
Julian Liebig  
Franz-Joseph-Str. 11  
80801 Munich  
EMail: support@workupload.com  
  
This contact data is therefore relevant for all data protection questions regarding this website and for all data protection claims on your part.  

B. Collection and storage of personal data when you visit our website

In the following, we will inform you about the relevant data protection procedures that take place when you visit our website.  

1\. Logfiles

Every time you visit our website, we automatically collect data and information from the computer system you use to access the website.  
  
The following data is collected here:  
  
(1) Information about your browser type and version  
(2) Information about your operating system  
(3) Date and time of your access  
(4) Websites from which your system accesses our website  
(5) Websites that are accessed by your system via our website  
(6) Your IP address  
  
Your data is processed for the purpose of delivering our website content, ensuring the functionality of our information technology systems, optimizing our website. Thus, the processing for the protection of our legitimate interest according to Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR, i.e. the performance of our business activities, is necessary.  
  
Since the collection of data for the provision of our website and the storage of data in log files is absolutely necessary for the operation of our website, you also have no right of objection.  

2\. Cookies

We use "cookies" on our website. These are small text files that your browser automatically creates and that are stored on your end device when you visit our website. Cookies do not damage your computer system or contain viruses, Trojan horses or other malicious software.  
  
We use cookies to improve our website, for example to make it more user-friendly and to adapt it to user interests.  
  
The following data will be stored and transmitted in the cookies:  
  
(1) Language settings  
(2) Login information  
(3) Frequency of page views  
(4) Usage of website functions  
  
The data collected in this way will be pseudonmyized as a technical precaution. It is therefore not possible to associate the data with you. The data will not be stored together with other personal data.  
  
The data processed by cookies is required for the purposes stated to safeguard our legitimate interests (the conduct of our business) pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR.  
  
Most browsers accept cookies automatically. To prevent this, however, you can configure your browser so that no cookies are stored on your computer system or so a message appears before a new cookie is created. However, if you disable cookies completely, you may not be able to use all the features of our website.  
  
Each browser may differ in the way it manages cookie settings. This is described in the help menu on each browser, which tells you how to change your cookie settings.  

3\. Advertising

We use "Google AdSense", an online advertising service from Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (hereinafter referred to as "Google"), on our website. Among other things, Google AdSense uses cookies, small text files that are stored locally in the cache of your web browser on your terminal device. For this Google uses a Web Beacon to set the cookies on your device. Your data will be transferred to the USA and evaluated there. If you are logged in with your Google account, your data can be directly assigned to it. If you don't want to be associated with your Google profile, you need to log out. It is possible that these data are passed on to contracting partners of Google to third parties and authorities.  
  
We use Google AdSense for the basic financing of this online offer. This also includes our legitimate interest in the processing of the above data by Google, which is based on Art. 6 para. 1 f) GDPR.  
  
You can revoke your consent to advertising here: Click here to revoke  
  
You can prevent the installation of cookies by deleting existing cookies and deactivating the storage of cookies in the settings of your web browser. We would like to point out that in this case you may not be able to use all the functions of our website. It is also possible to prevent the storage of cookies by deactivating the interest-related ads on Google via this link [http://www.google.de/ads/preferences](http://www.google.de/ads/preferences). Please note that this setting will be deleted if you delete your cookies. You can also deactivate interest-based ads via the link [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). Please note that this setting will be deleted if you delete your cookies. If you use the web browsers Firefox, Internet Explorer, or Google Chrome, you can permanently deactivate the setting of cookies under the following link: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin). We would also like to point out that in this case you may not be able to use all the functions of our website to their full extent.  
  
Google has also signed and is certified under the Privacy Shield Agreement between the European Union and the United States. Google therefore undertakes to comply with the standards and regulations of European data protection law. Further information can be found at the following link: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI)  
  
Further information on the use of data by Google, on setting and objection options and on data protection can be found on the following Google web page:  
  
• Privacy policy: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)  
• Privacy policy for advertising: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)  
• Data usage for advertising: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)  

C. Registration

You can register on our website in order to be able to use the full scope of the offer.  
  
The data you enter here will only be used for the purposes of using the offer. The data stored within the scope of the registration will not be passed on to third parties as long as this is not necessary for the fulfillment of the contractual purpose.  
  
When you register the following data will be stored:  
(1) Your IP address  
(2) Date and time of registration  
(3) Your email address  
  
The processing of the data provided is carried out for the fulfillment of the user contract in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 b) GDPR.  

D. Contact

You can contact us electronically via a form on the website or by email. In this case, the data that you enter in the form or send to us by email will be transmitted to us and stored by us.  
  
This concerns:  
  
(1) Date of contact  
(2) Your email address  
(3) If necessary, other data, if you provide this  
  
Before submitting the contact form, you will be advised of this privacy policy.  
  
If you write us an email and are interested in our offer, the legal basis for data processing is Art. 6 para. 1 b) GDPR. In all other respects the processing takes place due to our justified interest from Art. 6 para. 1 f) of the GDPR regarding business conduct.  
  
This data transmitted to us will only be used for the purpose of conducting the conversation and will not be passed on to third parties.  
  
We will delete this data if it is no longer required for the respective purpose. I.e. when the exchange by email or via the contact form with you is finished and we have completely processed your request.  

E. Processing in third countries in general

Unless otherwise stated above, the processing of your personal data in countries outside the European Union (EU) or the European Economic Area (EEA) is carried out exclusively on the basis of the legal requirements pursuant to Art. 44 GDPR. This is exclusively the case either on the basis of an adequacy decision of the European Commission (Art. 45 GDPR) and/or on the basis of appropriate guarantees (Art. 46 GDPR).  

F. General term of storage

In general, personal data will only be stored for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which the data was collected or to comply with the respective statutory retention period. After the purpose has been served or the deadline has expired, the data will be deleted.  

G. The data subject's rights

Insofar as we have processed personal data from you, you are a data subject within the meaning of the GDPR and you have the following rights towards us:  
(1) Art. 15 GDPR - You can request information about your personal data processed by us. In particular, you may obtain information about the purposes for which the data is processed, the category of personal data, the categories of recipients to whom your data has been or will be disclosed, the planned storage period, the existence of a right of rectification, deletion, limitation of processing or objection, the existence of a right of appeal, the origin of your data if it has not been collected from us, and the existence of automated decision making including profiling and, where applicable, the existence of a right of access to your data.  
(2) Art. 16 GDPR - You may immediately request the correction of inaccurate or incomplete personal data stored by us.  
(3) Art. 17 GDPR - You may request the deletion of your personal data stored with us, unless the processing is necessary for the exercise of the right to freedom of expression and information, to fulfill a legal obligation, for reasons of public interest or to assert, exercise, or defend legal claims.  
(4) Art. 18 GDPR - You may request the restriction of the processing of your personal data if the accuracy of the data is disputed by you, the processing is unlawful, but you refuse to delete it and we do not collect the data, however, you refuse the data deletion and we no longer need the data, but you need the data to assert, exercise or defend legal claims or you have lodged an objection against the processing pursuant to Art. 21 GDPR.  
(5) Art. 20 GDPR - You may receive your personal data which you have provided to us in a structured, common and machine-readable format or request transmission to another data controller.  
(6) Art. 7 para. 3 GDPR - You have the right to revoke your consent which you have granted to us at any time. The consequence of this is that we may no longer continue the data processing based on this consent for the future.  
(7) Art. 77 GDPR - You can lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. As a rule, you can contact the supervisory authority of your usual place of residence or workplace or our place of business.  

H. Right of Objection

If your personal data is based on legitimate interests pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 f) GDPR, you have the right in accordance with Art. 21 GDPR to object to the processing of your personal data if there are reasons for this which arise from your particular situation or if the objection is directed against direct advertising. In the latter case you have a general right of objection, which is implemented by us without stating a particular situation.  
  
If you wish to exercise your right of revocation or objection, simply send an email to support@workupload.com

I. DO NOT SELL MY PERSONAL INFORMATION

YOUR RIGHTS UNDER THE CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT  
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides you with rights regarding how your data or personal information is treated. Under the legislation, California residents can choose to opt out of the “sale” of their personal information to third parties. Based on the CCPA definition, “sale” refers to data collection for the purpose of creating advertising and other communications. [Learn more about CCPA and your privacy rights](https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa)  
**How to opt out**  
By clicking on the link below, we will no longer collect or sell your personal information. This applies to both third-parties and the data we collect to help personalize your experience on our website or through other communications. For more information, view our privacy policy.  
To be eligible to opt-out, you must be browsing from California.  

Choose Language

* * *

[General Terms and Conditions](https://workupload.com/legal/terms) [Privacy Policy](https://workupload.com/legal/privacy) [Imprint](https://workupload.com/imprint) [Digital Services Act](https://workupload.com/legal/dsa) [Do Not Sell My Personal Information](https://workupload.com/legal/privacy) online since 2011
